<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="5526" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mystical Ninja Starring Goemon (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Mystical Ninja Starring Goemon</name>
		<desc>The people of Oedo Town are in a panic!  A gigantic UFO shaped like a peach has arrived, and the Peach Mountain Shoguns have turned Oedo Castle into one big stage for themselves to perform on!  Everyone's relying on Goemon to save the day, but he hasn't even noticed what's happening!  Can our hero stop the Shoguns before they do any more damage?

Mystical Ninja Starring Goemon is an action-based RPG similar in style to The Legend of Zelda: The Ocarina of Time.  It is also the first localized Goemon game since The Legend of the Mystical Ninja for the SNES.  Players control Goemon and his friends as they make their way through Ancient Japan to stop the Peach Mountain Shoguns.  You can talk to characters, whack enemies with your pipe (or hurl coins at them), visit a deranged fortune teller who shrieks out "PLASMA!" at random intervals for no reason, and more.

Each member of the Goemon team can also learn a special ability to access new areas as players progress through the game.  Goemon earns the "Sudden Impact" power, which lets him move blocks he normally couldn't, Ebisumaru can shrink to small sizes so he can pass through tiny cracks, Sasuke earns an extra high jump, and Yae gets the ability to transform into a Mermaid so that she can swim underwater.

As usual, the gigantic roller-skating robot, Impact, makes an appearance.  Players get to use him to trample down buildings and duke it out in first-person mode against gigantic mecha boss characters in a Punch-Out!! style game.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Adventure-Adventure-Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash />
		<image>./media/images/Mystical Ninja Starring Goemon (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5561" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Power Rangers - Lightspeed Rescue (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Saban's Power Rangers : Lightspeed Rescue</name>
		<desc>POWER RANGERS RESCUE READY! The Power Rangers are saving the world on Nintendo 64! Rescue innocent people from the battlings. Drive cool Power Rangers vehicles! Fight huge monsters in awesome environments. Battle against your friends in the Megazord Arena!</desc>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>20000928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mass Media</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash />
		<image>./media/images/Power Rangers - Lightspeed Rescue (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5487" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Carmageddon 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Carmageddon 64</name>
		<desc>In Carmageddon, the player races a vehicle against a number of other computer controlled competitors in various settings, including city, mine and industrial areas. The player has a certain amount of time to complete each race, but more time may be gained by collecting bonuses, damaging the competitors' cars or by running over pedestrians.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Carmageddon 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>19991205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>SCi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="5422" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Worms Armageddon (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Worms Armageddon</name>
		<desc>The final sequel (at least using the present engine) to the strategy game Worms, Worms Armageddon expands on Worms 2 by improving quite a few facets of gameplay and including play over the Internet through Team 17's WORMNET. 

For those who've never played Worms, it's at heart similar to the old game Artillery, which you control an artillery piece. In essence, you give it a shot angle and shot power, and try to hit your enemy, despite wind effects and the enemy firing back at you. Worms puts you in command of a team of Worms, but not only can you move around the landscape, you can use many types of weapons to try to dispatch the enemy, from bazookas to mini-guns to exploding sheep. 

Everything is presented in a humorous cartoonish style, from the landscapes to the worms themselves and their cries of triumph or despair, depending on how you do.

Armageddon uses an enhanced version of the Worms 2 engine, and while an improvement over Worms 2, it's not a huge change.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Worms Armageddon (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="5563" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./FIFA Soccer 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>FIFA 64</name>
		<desc>The FIFA series introduces itself to the Nintendo 64, with all the football/soccer action one can expect from an EA Sports title. Choose your team, whether it be Manchester Utd or Real Madrid, or even a lowly ranked team, and take them through the ranks of the professional sport right up to the crowned kings of their tournament. You can stick with the local leagues (five in all) or take your team onto the International circuit and compete against every team available.

FIFA Soccer 64 can be played by up to 4 players at a time.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/FIFA Soccer 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19970301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>EA Sports</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer-Sports-Simulation</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="5634" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./GT64 - Championship Edition (USA).7z</path>
		<name>GT 64: Championship Edition</name>
		<desc>GT 64, short for Grand Tour 64, is a 3D racing game for the Nintendo 64. It features cars and drivers from the All-Japan GT Championship season of 1997 as it is an officially licensed game.

There are three stages with each a long and a short version counting six tracks in total situated in Japan, the USA and Europe. All of them are located in urban settings. You can opt to race three, six, twelve or 24 laps on each track. There are fourteen cars available to race in and they can be manually tweaked to improve performance.

The Japanese re-release of the game includes two new tracks based on the 1998 season.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/GT64 - Championship Edition (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineer</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ms. Pac-Man - Maze Madness (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Ms. Pac-Man : Maze Madness</name>
		<desc>Chomp your way through mystical worlds to save Pac-Land. Free the last worlds of Pac-Land fromt he horrid witch Mesmeralda. Videogame's favorite heroine is back to save the day!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Ms. Pac-Man - Maze Madness (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth-Puzzle-Game-Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T131708</lastplayed>
		<gametime>702</gametime>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RR64 - Ridge Racer 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Ridge Racer 64</name>
		<desc>Ridge Racer makes its first appearance on a Nintendo console, including all of the fast, pick up and play action previously seen in the series on Playstation and in arcades.

RR64 includes three tracks, each with three variations, making a total of nine tracks to get through. 25 cars are on offer, each with different power and speed abilities.

Single player and multiplayer modes are included. Beat the clock and get to the finish line first to win.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/RR64 - Ridge Racer 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T132831</lastplayed>
		<gametime>408</gametime>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Road Rash 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Road Rash 64</name>
		<desc>First version of Road Rash for any Nintendo system.  The game was originally supposed to be a port of Road Rash 3D but ended up being an original product.  Like other Road Rash titles, it featured motorcycle racing and combat, although RR64 had more of an emphasis on combat than on racing.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Road Rash 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pacific Coast Power &amp; Light</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T133220</lastplayed>
		<gametime>2091</gametime>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem 64</name>
		<desc>Duke Nukem 3D makes its way to the N64 for the first time, with plenty of new additions:

Weapons: New weapons include two sub-machine guns (one in each hand), the Expander (the bad guys just go pop!) a plasma cannon (which is chargeable) and a grenade launcher. Sadly, there are a few missing from the original PC version, including the Ripper Chaingun, the Devastator, and the Freeze-Ray.

Presentation: The biggest changes come here, as there are new areas to explore, some improved environments, and the same wise cracks that have made Duke famous. There are also some jokes hidden away based on classic movies (Clockwork Orange, 12 Monkeys, Mars Attacks and Apocalypse Now).

However, there have been plenty of restrictions in this version of Duke 3D. Nintendo have replaced some areas (the porn mag shop has turned into a gun store, the bar is now a burger joint, and the nude women aren't nude anymore), and there is an option available to turn the blood off.

A 4 player mode has also been included, where you can take on your mates as well as Duke Bots, and a 2 player co-op mode, so two players can tackle the single player missions.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Duke Nukem 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>3D Realms</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter-Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T104050</lastplayed>
		<gametime>326</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chopper Attack (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Chopper Attack</name>
		<desc>In Chopper Attack, you take a chopper and.. well.. attack! You get to choose between eight different attack choppers, each having its own strengths and weaknesses. 

After the briefing from your XO, you are set to destroy something - tanks, other helicopters, planes, radars, buildings etc. While the mission only requires you to do something specific, destroying everything gives you bonuses and money, which you can then use to buy more heavy-duty missiles between the missions.

If you look at the screenshots, you might think that Chopper Attack is a helicopter simulation. It's not. Your elevation is fixed. There are no physics. You have boss fights with GIANT choppers. The game is pure 3D action, plain and simple.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Chopper Attack (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SETA Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person-Shooter-Race, Driving</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T095859</lastplayed>
		<gametime>295</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania (USA) (Rev B).7z</path>
		<name>Castlevania</name>
		<desc>Konami's long-running series of Castlevania games makes its debut on the N64. The traditional 2D graphics have been left behind; this is the first Castlevania game in 3D. However, the goal of the game remains the same: kick some vampire butt as you battle the evil Count Dracula and his minions in this platformer.

The player can either choose to be Reinhardt Schneider (for the traditional whip action) or Carrie Fernandez (who uses magical powers). Both characters have their own story line. A nice feature is the presence of an in-game clock which changes the time of the day (either day or night).

Reinhardt &amp; Carrie both appear again in the second Castlevania game for the N64: Castlevania: Legacy of Darkness, which has new layouts for the levels of this game.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Castlevania (USA) (Rev B).png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action / Adventure-Action-Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T094221</lastplayed>
		<gametime>516</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monopoly (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Monopoly</name>
		<desc>This time, a Monopoly game on your computer, as good as it knows to be in your reality. Every move of yours can be in 3D animation, or off if you don't want to see animations. There can be up to 6 players at once, and it can be played over the Internet. Music is in midi format, and the sound quality is at the wav format. Roll, spin, and don't miss to give us a grin.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Monopoly (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minds Eye Production</developer>
		<publisher>Hasbro Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Board game-Strategy-Various</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T130507</lastplayed>
		<gametime>691</gametime>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gex 64 - Enter the Gecko (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Gex 64 : Enter the Gecko</name>
		<desc>The ultimate free-roaming 3D experience! 24 Media Dimension levels, all designed as sarcastic parodies of popular TV and movies! Master of Disguise GEX sports a secret agent suit, kung fu uniform, spacesuit and other costumes on his quest to save TV from the evil Rez! Over 125 slick gecko moves. Whip-cracking tail attacks, flying karate kicks, tongue-grabbing and climbing up walls. All-new N64 exclusive deep sea level with new swim mechanics and scuba gear!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Gex 64 - Enter the Gecko (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19980801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Associates</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T113950</lastplayed>
		<gametime>263</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fighters Destiny (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Fighters Destiny</name>
		<desc>Take a collection of fist-fighters, wrestlers and martial arts experts, and combine them into one tournament. But instead of relying on simply depleting the health bar, you must win points depending on how you defeat an opponent (for example, ring-outs are 1 point, special moves 4 points and countering a special move is 2 points). 

Game modes include the standard VS. mode, simply defeat everyone you see. VS. Battle allows you to defeat the enemy, then acquire their moves for the next round. The Master Challenge has you spinning a wheel to determine who your fight. Spin up a Master, and you get a tough challenge in which you can win new moves. Spin a Joker, and you simply have a challenge, with nothing to gain, but everything to lose.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Fighters Destiny (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19980131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Opus</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T113459</lastplayed>
		<gametime>553</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok - Dinosaur Hunter (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Turok : Dinosaur Hunter</name>
		<desc>Much like your usual 1st person shooter, although with dinosaurs as your main enemy. Includes 14 high tech weapons, like the Quad Rocket Launcher and the Atomic Fusion Cannon. You control Turok, who must take on the Campaigner and his highly evolved dino's. The objective is to collect pieces of the Chronoscepter, which is the only weapon that can help to destroy the Campaigner, and to stop him from using the power of the weapon to destroy the Lost Land.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Turok - Dinosaur Hunter (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person-Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T142746</lastplayed>
		<gametime>411</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Earthworm Jim 3D (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Earthworm Jim 3D</name>
		<desc>Earthworm Jim gets squashed by a cow, leaving him dazed and confused. In the aftermath, his marbles go missing, so he must travel into his brain to find them and put everything right. All of the laughs are there from the original platform titles, but now in huge 3D worlds.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Earthworm Jim 3D (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>VIS Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T104632</lastplayed>
		<gametime>615</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon 64</name>
		<desc>In Harvest Moon 64, your objective is to restore a run-down farm that you've inherited from your grandfather, who has died recently.  In the village many people help you out on your long journey.  During this time you can attend festivals, race in horse races, farm, tend to your livestock, add to your house, get married, or maybe even have a child.  There are 5 beautiful women to be chosen from, each having their own jobs and personalities.  At the end the player's parents come by and rate them after 2 and a half years of performance.  The option then exists either to keep going or stop there.  The real question is if you're up for the challenge.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Harvest Moon 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Victor Interactive Software</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T115811</lastplayed>
		<gametime>169</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cruis'n World (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Cruis'n World</name>
		<desc>Pack your bags and prepare for a first class trip around the world. Your ticket is courtesy of Midway, who has transformed its arcade mega-hit Cruis'n World into an all-new racer for the N64. 

Cruis'n USA thrilled racers with a scenic trip across the highways of America, but this time the action will take you all around the world. Each track is packed full of realistic scenery and authentic landmarks, so playing this game could save you a lot of dough on travel expenses. You can catch a glimpse of the Sphinx, the Statue of Liberty, and the Mayan ruins without leaving the security of your living room couch. 

 If you're looking for a realistic racing simulation with real world physics, then this is definitely not the game for you. The graphics are realistic, but the actual game play is twisted to the extreme. Even though blazing across the Great Wall of China may be unbelievable, it certainly is fun. You can leap-frog over a semi truck with a police car, or perform a back flip with a military ATV. Add to this a bonus race that takes place on the moon, and you have a good idea of Midway's over-the-top execution of the Cruis'n concept. 

Many of us will never get the chance to visit the Egyptian pyramids, let alone the opportunity to drive a screaming ambulance straight through them. Cruis'n World provides fun fantasy racing action, and the best thing about it is that you won't have to worry about your luggage getting left behind in Russia.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Cruis'n World (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19980928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T100437</lastplayed>
		<gametime>1221</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Kirby 64 : The Crystal Shards</name>
		<desc>Dart past enemies, soar the skies and swim the depths of the ocean as Kirby takes on Dark Matter in an all-new adventure. Inhale, exhale and swallow your enemies, then copy and combine their abilities and use them as your own! Team up with familiar friends and foes - like Waddle Dee and King Dedede - as you travel through dreamy worlds in search of the lost Crystal Shards.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T122306</lastplayed>
		<gametime>971</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Mega Man 64</name>
		<desc>Mega Man blasts his way onto the Nintendo® 64 System for the first time ever! This epic adventure combines the best of classic Mega Man action with enormous bosses, a riveting storyline and all the depth of the hottest RPG. Explore vast 3-D worlds in your quest to find the treasure of all treasures, the Mother Lode. You'll love the stunning 3-D graphics, powerful weapons and non-stop action ...unless of course, you're a boos.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Mega Man 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20010110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Sports</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T124728</lastplayed>
		<gametime>692</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./San Francisco Rush - Extreme Racing (USA).7z</path>
		<name>San Francisco Rush : Extreme Racing</name>
		<desc>Put the pedal to the metal, smoke the tires, and pour on the speed with San Francisco Rush! Hit the road in one of eight unique race cars ranked in four distinct performance classes. Burn rubber through the 3D modeled hills and landmarks of San Francisco. Choose from six accurately detailed tracks that can be adjusted with the games "Mirror" or "Backwards" options for a total of 24 incredible tracks! Spectacular hidden shortcuts on each track!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/San Francisco Rush - Extreme Racing (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T134126</lastplayed>
		<gametime>541</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to the award winning PSX and N64 title, Tony Hawk 2 adds heaps of new tricks, as well as those from the original, and a complete roster of all the greatest skaters worldwide. Fly through some of the greatest skate parks in the world, or create your own, and share them with your mates. You can also create your own skater, with a choice of clothing and official skateboards. Improved graphics and a choice of alternative or hip-hop music add to the endless options and full on action.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Edge Of Reality</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard-Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T142020</lastplayed>
		<gametime>219</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mystical Ninja 2 - Starring Goemon.7z</path>
		<name>Mystical Ninja Starring Goemon 2</name>
		<desc>Goemon and his friends return in this side-scrolling sequel to Mystical Ninja Starring Goemon.  Bismaru, who looks like Goemon's friend Ebisumaru dressed up as a nun, has swiped a freshly-invented Ghost Returning Machine!  With it, he's using planning nothing less than world domination.  All Ebisumaru wanted to do with it was meet his ancestor, James Dean!  Help Goemon and his friends retrieve the Machine, and bust some ghosts on the way.

Mystical Ninja 2 reverts back to the traditional side-scrolling 2D platforming style of the SNES games.  However, due to to the Nintendo 64's 3D capabilities, you'll encounter massive bosses and detailed worlds as you make your way through Japan.  To attack, you can either hurl coins, or use each character's specific weapon, such as Goemon's trademark pipe.  Two players can also play simultaneously and work together to beat foes, and you can even ride piggy-back onto your friend.

There are also towns to explore, where you chat with villagers and explore various shops and houses for information and clues.  Goemon Impact, the giant singing robot wearing rollerskates, also makes a return as you battle enemy mechs from inside its cockpit in a first-person view.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Mystical Ninja 2 - Starring Goemon.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Adventure-Action-Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T132308</lastplayed>
		<gametime>433</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hercules - The Legendary Journeys (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Hercules - The Legendary Journeys</name>
		<desc>Take control of the legendary hero Hercules and his friends Iolaus and Serena as they attempt to stop Ares from completing his diabolical plans. Use each character's unique attributes: Hercules' legendary strength, Iolaus' nimble nature and Serena's accuracy to complete your quest. Travel through 12 unique fully 3D worlds, from the sunny seaside town of Porticus to the snowy mountains of Alpsius. Explore the bandit-overrun forrests of Traycus or heavenly Mount Olympus. Fight mythical terrifying monsters such as the Minotaur, Cyclops, and more!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Hercules - The Legendary Journeys (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20001116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Player 1</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure-Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T120236</lastplayed>
		<gametime>260</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman 64 - The Second Attack! (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Bomberman 64 : The Second Attack!</name>
		<desc>Of the great discoveries in the universe, few are more important than the legendary 8 elements. When the evil Rukifellth found one of these elements - the powerful Celestial Stone - he used his influence to assemble the dreaded BHB Army. Armed with his new army and a giant space warship, the power-crazed Rukifellth began scouring the galaxy for the other 7 elements, invading planets and enslaving innocent races throughout the galaxy. Rukifellth controls these enslaved planets with special Gravity Generators - the same devices the BHB Army used to create a Black Hole. Rukifellth uses his Black Hole to capture new planets... But he should have thought twice before he tried to capture Bomber Planet!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Bomberman 64 - The Second Attack! (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000528T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Vatical Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T092335</lastplayed>
		<gametime>325</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Hero (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Bomberman Hero</name>
		<desc>This is another game in Bomberman series. Now you have to prevent the demolishing of Planet Bomber by evil Nitros and to acquire a computer disk from robot Pibot. As always you have to place the bomb in right location to destroy enemies, breaking walls, etc.
Here are the five different planets, 71 levels, 20 useful items, several special vehicles and your bombs.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Bomberman Hero (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AI</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T092746</lastplayed>
		<gametime>247</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diddy Kong Racing (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev A).7z</path>
		<name>Diddy Kong Racing</name>
		<desc>It's an island takeover when the evil space wizard, Wizpig, discovers Tiger Island!  After the islands prized racetracks become sealed up, Timber Tiger contacts his friend Diddy Kong to help him reclaim the racetracks and save the island before his parents return.  Along for the ride are the Kremling spy Krunch, Bumper Badger, Banjo (prior to meeting Kazooie in Banjo-Kazooie), pre-sweary Conker, Tiptup Turtle, and Pipsy Mouse.

Diddy Kong Racing is a racing game with similarities to Mario Kart 64, in that you race with a variety of cheery racers while using weapons.  However, the similarities end there.  DKR includes an adventure mode, which features bosses, an overworld to explore, many hidden secrets, the addition of hovercrafts and planes, and a unique way of racing called the "Silver Coin Challenge".  In this mode, in addition to coming first, you must also find the eight Silver Coins deviously hidden throughout the courses (some in alternate paths).

The game also features a strategic method of using weapons.  Each colored balloon on the track matches a specific weapon, and collecting the same type of balloon multiple times in a row powers it up (to a maximum of three times).  This gives the player the choice of snatching every balloon available and using it immediately, or storing the existing weapon, and using a more powerful version of it later.

Up to four players can compete in the races, but in order to play new tracks, they must first be unlocked in the single player game.  There are also four battle modes of play - two standard deathmatch maps, a capture-the-flag style battle where you must nab eggs and hatch three of them in your home nest, and another where you must be the first to return ten bananas to your treasure chest (with the limitation of only being able to hold two at any one time).</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Diddy Kong Racing (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev A).png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19971124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Rareware</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure-Race, Driving-Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T101722</lastplayed>
		<gametime>783</gametime>
		<lang>fr,en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev A).7z</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie</name>
		<desc>Banjo-Kazooie's fairy tale back story is reminiscent of Snow White's. A gnarled, ugly witch named Gruntilda asks her magical cauldron who is the fairest of them all. Of course, the pot's answer doesn't please the hag-- he singles out Banjo's sister, Tooty. When Tooty turns up missing, Banjo and his birdie buddy Kazooie set out to find her. 

The worlds in Banjo-Kazooie are gigantic, and chock full of crazy items to collect. Musical Notes, Puzzle Pieces ("Jiggies"), Mumbo Tokens, and Jinjoes are just some of the swag that Banjo must stuff in his backpack to complete his adventure. While some of the necessary items are simply stashed off the beaten path, others will require puzzle solving skills to turn up.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action / Adventure-Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T091806</lastplayed>
		<gametime>478</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chameleon Twist 2 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Chameleon Twist 2</name>
		<desc>After finding his way back home from his first adventure, Davy decides to relax with his friends. However, while playing on the see-saw, a huge rabbit falls from the sky, sending Davy head long into the sky. So once again, using his long tounge to attack enemies and grab onto distant ledges, Davy must find his way home from the land in the sky.

For the second adventure, you can now choose from 4 different Chameleon's, Davy and friends Linda, Fred and Jack. 
And as well as using his tongue, Davy can also use a parasol to float across large gaps.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Chameleon Twist 2 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Japan System Supply</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T095400</lastplayed>
		<gametime>878</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./South Park - Chef's Luv Shack (USA).7z</path>
		<name>South Park : Chef's Luv Shack</name>
		<desc>It's one big multi-player luv-in! All your favorite South Park characters are waiting for you at Chef's Luv Shack. Spreading the hot buttered game lovin' with dozens of crazy mini-games. Testing your South Park knowledge with outrageous trivia questions. And telling it like it is with insane sound-bites! Featuring authentic voices from South Park including Isaac Hayes as Chef!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/South Park - Chef's Luv Shack (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T134409</lastplayed>
		<gametime>357</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney's Tarzan (U) [!].7z</path>
		<name>Tarzan</name>
		<desc>Tarzan é um jogo de plataforma desenvolvido pela Eurocom para Nintendo 64 e distribuido pela Activision em 1999. O jogo se trata do filme de animação Tarzan da Disney, com gráficos cartunescos e ação lateral 2.5D.
O jogo coloca você em um papel de Tarzan, um futuro rei da selva, te leva a um monte de níveis de missões onde você pode coletar moedas, mapear peças, cartas de 'TARZAN' e outras coisas, bem como te chamar de amigo macaco de tempos em tempos, isso te dará uma breve explicação das coisas que estão por aí. Após cada nível completo, haverá animações breves que provavelmente tiraram do desenho animado da Disney, algumas dessa animações podem ser desbloqueadas acessando áreas secretas dentro do jogo.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Disney's Tarzan (U) [!]-image.png</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T140300</lastplayed>
		<md5>d39d9c4be17e7fdf17e13a6cd1a19863</md5>
		<gametime>638</gametime>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero X (USA).7z</path>
		<name>F-Zero X</name>
		<desc>Famed SNES racer F-Zero got this N64 update. Gameplay remains essentially unchanged, race in a futuristic racing tournament on tracks levitated miles up in the air, against a selection of devious opponents.

Where the original had 4 cars to choose from and race against, F-Zero X has no fewer than 30 vehicles all with their own unique strengths and weaknesses, a choice of colours, and customisable power/acceleration ratios for each track. At the beginning you are limited to choosing from 6 cars and 3 tournaments (each featuring 6 tracks each), but in true Nintendo fashion, more cars and tracks are unlocked as you progress through the game. As well as the cups, you can also race in time trial mode, against a 'ghost car' recording of your best previous lap, a lá Mario Kart 64.

Gone are the entirely flat tracks of the original, having been replaced with tracks that twist, turn, loop, rotate and basically contort into the most crazy shapes you could imagine. One unique feature amongst almost all other racing games is the "X" tournament, where courses are totally randomly generated each time you start.

One of the most important changes to the format is the inclusion of multiplayer support for up to 4 players. The various combat moves are especially important against aggressive human play.

This game has a  rock soundtrack, which I believe is the first game soundtrack ever to feature the bestial grunting found only in death metal music.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/F-Zero X (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220912T112542</lastplayed>
		<gametime>2331</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doom 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Doom 64</name>
		<desc>DOOM 64 picks up where all the other DOOM games left off. After tearing through space, hell, and wherever else in the previous games, the  Space Marine thought that the threat of the demons was finally past. Of course, one survived, and it is currently reanimating all of the fallen monsters in a last-ditch attempt to revitalize their evil mission. The player's task is to finally rid the universe of all the crazy hellions, from the dead guy with the pistol to the rocket-spewing Cyberdemon.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Doom 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter-Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220915T092021</lastplayed>
		<gametime>3367</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Indy Racing 2000 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Indy Racing 2000</name>
		<desc>Indy Racing 2000 is an officially licensed product of that year's Indy Racing League. At this point it purely raced on oval tracks, and featuring Indianapolis-style race cars - open wheel, open cockpit.

All 20 drivers and their cars and teams are authentic with fully licensed IRL tracks including night time tracks at Texas and Charlotte. Two player mode is supported and there is a unique draft meter to aid in making sling-shot moves for passing.

Top drivers are represented with detailed replicas of their cars. It is a racing simulation rather than a pure action game, letting you choose the angles of the front wing, rear wing, set the tire pressure, gear ratios and transmission type.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Indy Racing 2000 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20000609T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paradigm Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220915T092451</lastplayed>
		<gametime>604</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Looney Tunes - Duck Dodgers.7z</path>
		<name>Daffy Duck Starring as Duck Dodgers</name>
		<desc>Marvin The Martian has developed an ultimate weapon that will allow him to finally destroy Earth, which will ultimately allow him to take control of the universe. Upon the demonstration of the weapon, a slight snag hinders Marvin from completing his devious deed. The Weapon is out of Atoms, which it runs on, so he sends his minions (All of which are characters from the Looney Tune universe) to gather Atoms to fuel his weapon. 
 
Duck Dodgers is informed by his academy of Marvin's deeds and sets out to find the one-hundred Atoms before Marvin can. This ultimately has Dodgers and his sidekick, Cadet, trekking to four different planets, including a large pirate ship, to obtain the upper-hand over Marvin.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Looney Tunes - Duck Dodgers.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paradigm Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Platform</genre>
		<playcount>10</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220915T084600</lastplayed>
		<gametime>2315</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Micro Machines 64 Turbo (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Micro Machines 64 Turbo</name>
		<desc>With a quirky mix of toy car racers and sophisticated gameplay, Micro Machines 64 Turbo guarantees to be a refreshing addition to the stable of standard racing games. The wide variety of vehicles featured includes Formula 1 racers, speed boats, monster trucks, tanks, and ice cream trucks. Choose from 25 whimsical tracks, which run the gamut from a kitchen table to a chemistry lab, each including the appropriate props to match the d¿cor. Such detail rich touches keep this game interesting, even to the most jaded gamer. Belying the kiddie car appearance, the game requires you to plan strategically if you want to emerge the winner, making good use of the weapons at your disposal.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Micro Machines 64 Turbo (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220915T093338</lastplayed>
		<gametime>727</gametime>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AeroGauge (USA).7z</path>
		<name>AeroGauge</name>
		<desc>Blaze through the skies as you take control of your very own Aeromachines in this new futuristic racing game, AeroGauge. With courses that have sharp turns, and even sharper obstacles, it is going to take a keen eye and ultimate control to maneuver through courses featuring canyons, tunnels, oceans, and mountains. Imagine speeds reaching over 1000 mph as you whiz by the field in route to victory in these graphically advanced landscapes. Never has a game incorporated such remarkable control, detailed graphics, and mind-tingling speeds as... AeroGauge!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/AeroGauge (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19980430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Locomotive Games</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220915T103445</lastplayed>
		<gametime>1758</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starfox 64 (U).7z</path>
		<name>Star Fox 64</name>
		<desc>The Lylat system has been invaded! Join Fox McCloud and his Star Fox team as they fight to save the galaxy from the clutches of the evil Andross. Travel to many different 3-D worlds. Battle the enemy in the air and on the ground and listen in as Fox McCloud interacts with a cast of characters.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Starfox 64 (U).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220915T100037</lastplayed>
		<gametime>1998</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./California Speed (USA).7z</path>
		<name>California Speed</name>
		<desc>California Speed has you racing through, of course, California, with a range of different and unique tracks based on the real life maps of the US state, with short-cuts and branching elements adding elements of strategy when racing to the finish line. Cars include the usual collection of fast cars, as well as F1 racers and golf-carts, and you can customize your car's paint job to suit your style.

Split screen two player racing is supported.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/California Speed (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19990228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>9</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T165232</lastplayed>
		<gametime>2066</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev A).7z</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Ocarina of Time (Rev A)</name>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule. He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce. As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf's evil schemes. Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora's Domain. Before you complete this epic quest, you'll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141231T182639</lastplayed>
		<gametime>1702</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev B).7z</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Ocarina of Time (Rev B)</name>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule. He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce. As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf's evil schemes. Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora's Domain. Before you complete this epic quest, you'll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141231T182639</lastplayed>
		<gametime>1702</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA).7z</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Ocarina of Time</name>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule. He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce. As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf's evil schemes. Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora's Domain. Before you complete this epic quest, you'll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141231T182639</lastplayed>
		<gametime>1702</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64</name>
		<desc>K. Rool has kidnapped the Kongs! Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky's Pineapple Launcher or Lanky's Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny's Ponytail Twirl. Even rocket to the sky with Diddy's Jetbarrel!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Donkey Kong 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Adventure-Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>8</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221110T074423</lastplayed>
		<gametime>3701</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64</name>
		<desc>Mario is super in a whole new way! Combining the finest 3-D graphics ever developed for a video game and an explosive sound track, Super Mario 64 becomes a new standard for video games. It's packed with bruising battles, daunting obstacle courses and underwater adventures. Retrieve the Power Stars from their hidden locations and confront your arch nemesis - Bowser, King of the Koopas!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Super Mario 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>12</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141231T180350</lastplayed>
		<gametime>18728</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).7z</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Majora's Mask</name>
		<desc>Thrown into a parallel world by the mischievous actions of a possessed Skull Kid, Link finds a land in grave danger. The dark power of a relic called Majora's Mask has wreaked havoc on the citizens of Termina, but their most urgent problem is a suicidal moon crashing toward the world. Link has only 72 hours to find a way to stop its descent.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<playcount>5</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20230127T094520</lastplayed>
		<gametime>3547</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 3 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Mario Party 3</name>
		<desc>The series continues with a set of 70 new mini-games.  Play in the new single-player Story mode, or bring in some friends for Party mode.  Four player games and a new two player mode are also available for play.

In Battle Royale mode (four player), you race around different boards to earn the most stars and coins.  At the end of each round, you face it off in one of the mini-games, which can be chicken chases, snowball fights, or various other competitions.

Duel mode allows play between just two people.  You still race around the board, but mini-games are only played when you land on a specific square.  Another play change is the addition of another character for your team, allowing tag team-style action in the game.

Story mode is essentially the same as a Battle Royale, except your opponents are played by the computer.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Party 3 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010507T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Board game-Action-Casual Game</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>5</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20230206T161527</lastplayed>
		<gametime>3112</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart 64 races eight familiar faces, including Mario, Bowser and Yoshi, on four progressively tougher four-track circuits. Wide curves and gentle banks mark the Mushroom Cup tracks. Your commute gets notably tougher on the Flower Cup, though. The player will have to dodge semis rumbling on Toad's Turnpike and bounding boulders on fogbound Choco Mountain! Star Cup tracks range from the icy surfaces of Sherbet Land to the lava lakes of Bowser's Castle. The true test of karting competence, though, comes on the four tracks in Special Cup. Zip through the dark caves and green hillsides of Donkey Kong's Jungle Parkway, cling to the sheer cliffs of Yoshi Valley and hustle over haunted Banshee Boardwalk before tackling the longest track in the game: neon-lit Rainbow Road. 

The game offers two camera angles and three engine sizes: 50cc, 100cc and 150cc. You can gain even more speed by mastering the power slide technique or grabbing Super Star power-ups. Each kart has distinctive handling, acceleration and top speed capabilities. Light karts like Princess's smoothly steer through tight corners, but run the constant risk of getting flattened by heavy karts, like Donkey Kong's. Shells that you fire at rival racers, Bananas that make them skid out and Lightning Bolts that make them small and very slow are just a few of the game's unique power-ups.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Kart 64 (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports-Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>15</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20230301T095622</lastplayed>
		<gametime>10677</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
</gameList>
